

□ (+98) 910-547-6014 | **☑** rezaqavi1379@gmail.com | **⑤** RezaQavi-git | **ⓑ** rezaqavi

"Every things happened, just let it go."

Summary

I am a recent graduate from the University of Tehran with a Bachelor's degree in Computer Engineering. I have experience in both front-end and back-end development, particularly with Python programming language. Additionally, I have more experience in data engineering concepts and working with data to create meaningful results from seemingly non-meaningful information. I am passionate about working with data and analysis to create meaningful insights.

Education

University of Tehran Tehran, Iran

BACHELOR OF Science in COMPUTER Engineering (SOFTWARE Engineering)

2018 - 2023

• Last two academic years' overall GPA: 18.26/20 (Total GPA: 16.89/20)

Shahid Beheshti High School, under the supervision of NODET (National Organization for Developing Exceptional Talents)

Qaen, Iran

DIPLOMA IN MATHEMATICS AND PHYSICS

2014-2018

• GPA: 19.98/20

Work Experience _____

Tapsi (aka Iranian Uber)

Tehran, Iran

Data Engineer June 2022 - Present

Tapsi is an online cab e-hailing and ride-sharing platform. Having hundreds of thousands of rides per day, its infrastructure has huge performance, network, and availability challenges.

SNL Laboratory University of Tehran

Tehran, Iran

INTERNSHIP

June 2022 - Sep 2022

• Spend my internship as a front-end developer at SNL laboratory university of Tehran and designed two websites with React JS for AI research in the laboratory about COVID-19.

Freelancer Job Websites Tehran, Iran

PART TIME

June 2022 - Sep 2022

· Several freelancer projects mostly with python programming language.

Skills

Programming, Python, Java, C, C++, Go, JavaScript, Bash

Technologies, Git, Linux, Docker, Spring, SQL, Rest API, Spark, Hadoop, Airflow

Familiar, Django, Databases, Scala, Verilog, DevOps, Kubernetes, NGNIX, Computer Networks, Design

Pattern:

Soft Skills, Creative, Motivated, Communicative, Hard-working, Organized, Introvert

Others, Object-Oriented Programming, Software Development Methodologies, Agile, Multi-Thread

Programming, Socket Programming, Big Data Proccessing, ETL

Selected Projects

Moodle - Introduction	to Computing Sy	stems and Programming.
Moodie - Illii oductioli	to Collibutilis 21	volenno aniu Programmining.

Fall 2018	Implemented a system for managing and manipulating courses, students, and grades Developed using	С
	linked list, memory allocation, and structs in C	
Spring	Netflix - Advanced Programming,	C++, HTML,
2019	Developed an OOP application like Netflix with C++ Implemented a simple UI using HTML and CSS	CSS
	Operating System Projects,	
Fall 2020	Developed a client-server application using socket programming via UDP and TCP protocol Developed a multi-process application and used named and unnamed pipes for IPC	C++
	Developed a multi-thread program using the Pthread library for calculating an AI model accuracy	
	Artificial Intelligence Projects,	
Spring 2021	Implemented several conscious and unconscious search algorithms for solving the snake and seed problem Implemented a genetic algorithm for designing a logic circuit with a given truth table Implemented a Naive Bayes Classifier for classifying an online shop's comments Implemented several simple machine learning regressions using scikit-learn to predict house prices	Python
	Implemented a neural network for COVID-19 diagnosis using CT scan images of lungs.	
	Computer Network Projects,	
Spring 2021	Developed a simple FTP-server application using socket programming Implemented a simple version of Ethernet switch	C++
	Implemented a simple version of a router for sending multicast messages	
	Bolbolestan - Internet Engineering,	
Spring 2021	A unit selection system web application like "Golestan" with MVC architecture Back-end developed using Spring and MySQL Front-end	Spring,MYSQL, ReactJS,Docker
	developed using ReactJS Application deployed using Docker and Kubernetes	
Spring	A5-1 - Computer Networks Security , Implemented both encryption and decryption modules for A5-1	Duthon
2022	stream cipher using Python	Python

Teaching Experience

Teaching Assistant of Introduction to Computing Systems and Programming

University of Tehran

SCHOOL OF ELECTRICAL AND COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Fall 2020

• Supervisor Prof. Hadi Moradi

Teaching Assistant of Internet Engineering

SCHOOL OF ELECTRICAL AND COMPUTER ENGINEERING

• Supervisor Prof. Ehsan Khamespanah

Teaching Assistant of Database Design Lab

SCHOOL OF ELECTRICAL AND COMPUTER ENGINEERING

• Supervisor Prof. Mojtaba Banaie

University of Tehran

Spring 2022

University of Tehran

Spring 2023

Language Proficiency

Persion, Native

English, Upper-intermediate

Arabic, Intermediate